

HAFIZ AMINSALIM

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL INFO

Address

Gribig Krajan rt03/01 Gebog Kudus, Jawa Tengah

Date of Birth

July 8th, 2003

ABOUT ME

I am a junior web developer. Passionate in web development and always willing to learn something new. I have experience at working on a project either it is from scratch or continuing someone's own, and have been able to work as a team or individually.

ACHIEVEMENT

1st place at LKS Web Design & Development Kudus - September, 2019

CONTACT & OTHER INFORMATION

Phone : 085719595896

Email: hafizamin8116@gmail.com

Telegram : t.me/hafizxd Github : github.com/hafizxd

EDUCATION

SMK Raden Umar Said, Kudus (Aug 2017 - May 2020)

Rekayasa Perangkat Lunak

EXPERIENCE

Internship

PT. Janish Lintas Data, Tangerang (Feb 2019 - Jul 2019)

- Helping the employee on building website
- Using Laravel and JQuery

Full Time (Back End Developer)

PT. Transisi Teknologi Mandiri, Sleman DIY (Jul 2020 -Apr 2021)

https://transisi.id/

- Mostly creating API to be implemented by the Front End Devs
- Using Laravel and following Repository Design Pattern

SKILLS

Front-end	Back-end
- HTML	- PHP
- CSS	- Laravel
- SASS/SCSS	- MySQL
- Javascript	
- JQuery	Other
- VueJS	
- Vuetify	- GIT
- Bootstrap	